(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),n=r.n(s),a=r(3),o=r.n(a),i=(r(9),r(1));function c(){var e=[{questionText:"Evaluate 1/15 + 4/5",answerOptions:[{answerText:"5/20",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1/4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"13/15",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"43/15",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Add the fractions 2/7 + 13/28",answerOptions:[{answerText:"3/7",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"3/4",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"15/35",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"22/28",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Determine the value of 5/21 + 1/3",answerOptions:[{answerText:"4/7",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"6/24",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1/4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"12/21",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"2/14 + 5/24",answerOptions:[{answerText:"7/68",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4/16",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"10/38",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"59/168",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"3/5 + 3/8",answerOptions:[{answerText:"19/20",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"39/40",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"6/13",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"9/40",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Determine the value of 2/12 + 2/4",answerOptions:[{answerText:"4/48",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1/4",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"2/3",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"1/12",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Add the fractions 2/7 + 1/4",answerOptions:[{answerText:"2/14",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1/7",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"3/11",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"15/28",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Determine the value of 6/9 + 1/4",answerOptions:[{answerText:"7/13",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"1/6",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"6/36",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Add the fractions 1/4 + 2/5",answerOptions:[{answerText:"21/15",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"13/20",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"2/97",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"1/10",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"5/9 + 1/4",answerOptions:[{answerText:"6/13",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"29/13",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"5/36",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"29/36",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(s.useState)(0),r=Object(i.a)(t,2),a=r[0],o=r[1],c=Object(s.useState)(!1),w=Object(i.a)(c,2),x=w[0],T=w[1],u=Object(s.useState)(0),C=Object(i.a)(u,2),l=C[0],p=C[1];return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},x?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",l," out of ",e.length):n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},n.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",a+1),"/",e.length),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},e[a].questionText)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},e[a].answerOptions.map((function(t){return n.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&p(l+1);var r=a+1;r<e.length?o(r):T(!0)}(t.isCorrect)}},t.answerText)})))))}o.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(c,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(10)},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.258c8382.chunk.js.map